ausbt.com.au 2017-02-17

# Privacy - Australian Business Traveller

Australian Business Traveller is strongly committed to protecting your privacy while interacting with our content, products and services.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to tell you what kind of information we may gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct this information. Our policy allows you to choose what kind and how much information you provide to us and to control how we use whatever information you give us. Our goal is to provide you with a satisfying experience while allowing you to control your privacy and to give you a means to voice any questions or concerns you may have.

This policy applies only to Australian Business Traveller and not to other companies' or organisations' websites to which Business Travel Media Pty Ltd is linked.

 **Collection of information**

Information is collected from you primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked to provide information such as your name, email address, occupation, location or other personal information. It is entirely your choice whether to respond to these questions or requests for information.

Australian Business Traveller collects two types of information. The first type is anonymous information. For instance, we may collect information to tell us that five thousand people visit this Privacy Policy today, but we do not know their names, where they live or their date of birth - they are 'anonymous' to us. Another example of Australian Business Traveller collecting anonymous information is when visitors are invited to respond to surveys or polls on our website. The surveys may ask you for demographic information such as your age, gender and postcode. This information is collected for research purposes, is used in the aggregate (where possible), and remains anonymous. Many of the individuals who access our services are anonymous to us.

The second type of information that Australian Business Traveller collects is personal information. Australian Business Traveller will collect personal information that lets us know the specifics of who you are such as your name, email address, or postal address, when you provide it to us. With this information, Australian Business Traveller can provide a variety of personalised and enhanced services that are not available to anonymous users. We hope that you will find it beneficial to provide individually identifiable information about yourself to us because it will make our services more valuable to you and enhance your experience using our website.

Sometimes, we may specifically ask for personal information about you when you sign up to use a service. Certain information may be required, such as your name, age, internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number, in order to provide that service or product to you. This information may also be used to inform you of additional products and services which may interest you. You can choose not to receive such information when you are undertaking product or service registration on our website. We may also ask about your interests, but it is your choice whether to respond.

How much of your personal information that you choose to disclose to Australian Business Traveller is completely up to you. The only way we know something about you personally is if you provide it to us, for example when you take part in a discussion forum or enter one of the competitions on our websites.

 **Use of anonymous information**

Australian Business Traveller automatically gathers anonymous information to monitor the use of Australian Business Traveller like the numbers and frequency of visitors to Australian Business Traveller and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our audiences use parts of the site, so we can improve Australian Business Traveller to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many users as possible. Australian Business Traveller may publish or provide this aggregate data to other people.

 **Use of personal information**

Australian Business Traveller will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for which you provided it. Australian Business Traveller will not use it for any other purpose without your consent.

 **Disclosure**

There will be occasions where it will be necessary for Australian Business Traveller to disclose your personal information to third parties. Australian Business Traveller may be required by law to disclose the information, or we may be required to disclose your personal information to third parties to provide the service you have requested, for example, if you enter a competition for prizes provided by third parties. However, the disclosure will only be made where it is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which you disclosed your personal information. Otherwise than stated above, we do not disclose personal information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any organisation or person outside Australian Business Traveller unless you have authorised us to do so. For example, when you contribute to an online forum you may want to publish your name and email address.

 **Interacting with Australian Business Traveller**

There are many interactive features on Australian Business Traveller that you can contribute to. These include: Comments, Discussions, Reviews, Questions & Answers, Interviews, Online Voting, Community, Mailing Lists and Email, as well as others.

When interacting with Australian Business Traveller, we suggest that you use your discretion and exercise caution when providing your personal information.

Note that whenever you post personal information in publicly accessible places, such as comment threads or reviews, this information becomes available to anyone with access to the Internet. This information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Therefore, we recommend that you refrain from posting any information that you do not want seen in these public areas. For example, when participating in Australian Business Traveller’s interactive features, your name may appear on communications you send, provided that you have given it to us.

 **Security**

Australian Business Traveller will strive to protect your privacy and security as best we can. Ultimately, however, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any personal information.

 **Complaints about privacy**

If you have any complaints relating to online privacy issues on Australian Business Traveller, please notify one of our staff. While Australian Business Traveller accepts no liability for any material or links posted to the service, we will attempt to investigate all complaints.

 **Changes to Australian Business Traveller’s privacy policy**

If we decide to change the Australian Business Traveller’s Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here.
